<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GaysianThirdSpace</title>
    <link>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GaysianThirdSpace</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017 Gaysian Third Space, All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gaysianthirdspace.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Gaysian Third Space</title>
      <link>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Outside the clubs and beyond the apps, we aim to provide a Third Space&amp;mdash;a community to share, discuss, and provide support for the unique experience of being Gay and Asian.
Getting Involved There are many ways you can get involved in our community:
 Follow us on Tumblr, where we publish one post, article, or video every day! Read about our featured Follower profiles, or submit one! Want a gaysian mentor, or want to mentor a fellow gaysian?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We love hearing from people! If you have any questions about Gaysian Third Space, if you&amp;rsquo;d like to join our community, or if you&amp;rsquo;d like to work with us, please send us a message! You can message us by email, on our Tumblr blog, or on our Facebook page.
Tumblr You can send us a message on Tumblr through our Ask Box. By default, we post answers to all Ask Box questions to our blog, but you can request that we reply to you privately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetups</title>
      <link>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/meetups/</guid>
      <description>G3S has facilitated meetups all around the world! Our regional chapters in North America organize official social events, and we&amp;rsquo;ve also had informal meetups where people hang out together after meeting through G3S&amp;rsquo;s Tumblr, Facebook, or LINE Chat Group. Traveling somewhere and want to get to know some local G3S members? Contact the regional chapters below and get connected!
 Current Regional Chapters We have regional chapters of various sizes in several North American regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaysianthirdspace.com/programs/</guid>
      <description>One of the main missions at G3S is to create a supportive gaysian community and foster mentorship and friendship as we explore our identities. To fulfill this mission, we started by creating a Tumblr blog to share and archive content relevant to our community. To facilitate closer interactions, we created a LINE chat group for chatting and more casual conversation. In addition to these platforms, we have created a mentorship program for people to interact and learn from each other in an even smaller group setting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>